arlo.com 2017-06-30

# Privacy Policy | About Us | NETGEAR

  * Management Team
  * Careers
  * Press Releases
  * In the News
  * Environment
  * Regulatory/Export Compliance
  * Corporate Social Responsibility
  * Security Advisory
  * NETGEAR Gives Back
  * Trademarks
  * Events
  * Partners
  * Privacy Policy
  * Terms and Conditions
  * Ad & Cookie Policy
  * Warranty Information

#### This privacy policy applies to our sites and products.

This policy describes how NETGEAR, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates ("NETGEAR") treat certain personal information. This policy applies to the websites where it appears. It also applies to the products we sell. Some of those products include our routers and gateways. It also includes our ReadyNAS products and switches. In addition, it includes our Arlo and VueZone products.

##### We collect information from and about you.

**Contact information**. For example, we might collect your name and street address. We might also collect your phone number or email address. 

**Payment information**. For example, we collect your credit card number when you buy a subscription to use Arlo, for shipping services related to a warranty replacement, or when you buy/license an application from the NETGEAR App Marketplace. 

**Demographic information**. We may collect information about your interests or hobbies. We might also ask your sex or age. 

**Information you share or post on our website or through our systems**. For example, we collect information that you post in a public space on our website, such as message boards. As another example, you can choose whether to share your Arlo camera access through an invitation link that you can send to friends. Please see your Arlo account information at arlo.netgear.com to send invitation links and change your Arlo account settings. 

**Other Information**. If you use our website, we may collect information about your browser and what site you came from. We might also look at how often you use one of our applications. If you use our products, we might remotely monitor your usage. This could include gathering information and statistics about the performance of your NETGEAR devices. The kinds of things we look at include, for example, Internet speed and voltage information. We may also look at storage information, error rates, and other performance information.

##### We collect information in different ways.

**We collect information directly from you**. For example, if you sign up to be on our mailing list. We also collect information when you register a product or complete a survey. For our Arlo and VueZone products, we store the videos that you take with your systems for various time periods depending up the subscription plan that you have.

**We collect information from you passively** . We use tracking tools like cookies and web beacons. To learn more about how we use these tools, click here . We collect information about users over time when you use this website. We may have third parties collect personal information this way. We also collect information from our devices like the Usage Information described above. 

**We combine information.** For example, we may combine information we get from a third party with information we already have.

##### We use information as disclosed and described in this document.

**We use information to respond to your requests or questions**. For example, if you ask for a whitepaper we will send it to you. We might use your information to confirm your subscription. We will also give you technical support if you are eligible for it. When we provide support, we may use the information you provided or information we’ve gathered passively. 

**We use information to communicate with you about our relationship**. We may contact you about your account or subscription. We may contact you about this Policy or our website Terms. 

**We use information to improve our website or our products and services**. For example, we might conduct surveys so we know our customers. We might use your information to customize your experience with us or to improve our products and services. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties. 

**We use information for marketing purposes**. For example, we might send you special promotions or offers. We might also tell you about new features or products. These might be our own offers or products, or offers for third-party products we think you might find interesting. We may track your activities and show you ads we think you might like. 

**We use information for security purposes**. We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our websites. 

**We use information to talk to parents or guardians to get permission**. We may use contact information to get permission from parents for children who want to use our site. 

**We use information as otherwise permitted by law.**

##### We may share information with third parties.

**We will share information within the NETGEAR family of companies**. This includes our European affiliates, for example. 

**We may share information with third parties who provide services for us**. For example, we share information with vendors who help us send emails and operate our websites. We also share information to fulfill your purchases. Some vendors may be located outside of the United States. 

**We may share information with our business partners**. For example, share information with our partners that run our applications. 

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business**. For example, if all or part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction. 

**We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves**. For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may also share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. **We might also share information when we are investigating potential fraud. We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you**.

##### You have certain choices about our marketing and tracking tools.

**You can opt out of receiving our marketing and promotional emails**. To stop receiving our marketing and promotional emails, click [here](http://echo4.bluehornet.com/clients/netgear/unsubscribe.htm) or follow the instructions in any marketing email you get from us. Don’t worry! Even if you opt-out of getting marketing and promotional emails, we will still be sure to send you important transactional messages. For example, we may still contact you about your orders, you will also continue to receive critical technical information about your NETGEAR products, and Arlo will continue to send you notifications depending on the system settings that you implement. 

**We do not share information with third parties for their independent marketing or promotional purposes**. 

**You can control cookies and tracking tools**. To learn how to control these, visit our About our Ads section. 

**You can choose not to install our applications or fill out a warranty card**. This choice may limit your warranty service. 

##### We participate in the U.S.-EU and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Programs

NETGEAR, Inc. participates in the U.S.-E.U. and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Programs. We have certified that we comply with the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce, regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. For more information about the Safe Harbor program and to view our certification, click [here](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

##### These sites and children. 

Our sites and apps are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or guardian and you think your child under 13 has given us information, please [contact us](mailto:privacy.policy@netgear.com). 

Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children’s privacy on-line [here](http://onguardonline.gov/articles/0031-kids%E2%80%99-privacy). 

Certain of NETGEAR’s products are also equipped with parental control features. To learn more about them, click here.

##### We use standard security measures.

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords. 

We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

##### We store information in and outside the United States.

If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States or our offices in other countries. Our sites are subject to U.S. laws, which may not provide the same level of protection as those in your country.

##### We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site we don’t control. 

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites.

##### Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.

You can reach us by using the information on our contact us page, or by email at [privacy.policy@netgear.com](mailto:privacy.policy@netgear.com).

If you want to correct or update your information with NETGEAR, Inc., please email us at [privacy.policy@netgear.com](mailto:privacy.policy@netgear.com).

If contacting us does not resolve the issue, you can raise the issue with the JAMS SafeHarbor@jamsadr.com.

##### We may update this policy.

From time to time we may change our privacy policy. We will tell you about any material changes to our policy. Please check our site for updates.
